Berkay Baltas

1951A 80th Street East Elmhurst, New York, 11370 | berkaybaltas@gmail.com | (347) 656 6679

PROFILE

Experienced operative in computer programming, who demonstrates an exquisite skillset which includes the ability to lead, organize efficiently, as well as analyze and design systems. Pursuing bachelors degree in computer information systems and maintaining in-depth knowledge of computer science theory.

EXPERIENCE

Troynetics, LLC - Software testing

October 2015 - 2017

- Contributing in a start-up company to build ecommerce platforms.
- Responsible for keeping developers up to date with software issues.
- Worked with developers overseas and tested software using HTML, CSS, JavaScript.

Independent Contractor- for (Uber, Lyft, Juno, Gett)

MARCH 2015 - Present

- Maintaining business expenses and revenues, while keeping vehicle documents up to date.
- Expresses positive attitudes, resulting in high ratings.
- Handles all vehicle maintenance and repairs.
- Transports passengers safely, and productively.

EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATIONS

William Cullen Bryant High School, 4810 31st Avenue

Phi Theta Kappa Honor Society – GPA 3.72

B.S Hunter College, 695 Park Ave, New York, NY 10065

A.A.S Queensborough Community College, 2205 56th Ave

Microsoft Office Specialist Access 2013

- September 2010 - June 2014

- August 2015 – May 2018

- September 2018 December 2019
- September 27th, 2018 Present

SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE

- Efficient in Microsoft Access, Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Windows 7, Windows 10, Windows XP, macOS.
- Designed many software solutions driving continuous improvement to processes, systems, and workflow.
- Developed and implemented databases using agile methodologies.
- Impressive leadership skills and qualities.
- Standard knowledge and experience on Python, VBA, HTML, JavaScript, CSS, Java, SQL. Competent on programming specifics.